question_data = [
    {
        "category": "History",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Spitfire originated from a racing plane.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The country song  'A Boy Named Sue' was written by Shel Silverstein.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Pablo Picasso is one of the founding fathers of &quot;Cubism.&quot;",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center because it was destroyed by "
                    "terrorist attacks according to the game's plot.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Norway has a larger land area than Sweden.",
        "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy "
                    "the supernatural area known as 'the Zone'.",
        "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "&quot;Neutral Milk Hotel&quot; is a real band.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "In The Witcher 3, the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Man's Tree.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    }
]
